Hello guys welcome to another video of stock
market friends III Prudential Life
Insurance has presented its September quarter
financial results
both the standard loan consolidated results are out
which is the second quarter and half year end
results and we will do the
analysis here and first
cover the consolidated financial results
which is both the second quarter and half year
results are out come on
friends we have come to the results the
numbers have been given in lax if we talk about income the income is
17526 crores whereas
in the previous quarter the
income was 2354 crores and in the September 22
quarter the
income was 22904 crores this time there has been a
huge decline in income whether it is
quarter on quarter or year on
year there has been a huge decline in income this
time the expenses which is
17226 crores in the previous quarter there was
2334 crores and in the September 22 quarter there was an
expense of 2381 crores
because in the quarter on  Quarterly
expenses are also down but year on year
expenses are also down, which means that
expenses according to income have also come down here. If we
talk about profit before tax in quarter on quarter year on year, then it is
down in 247.com. If we talk about profit after
tax here, then here the
operating net profit is Rs 2438 crore, which was Rs
206 crore in the previous quarter
and Rs 200 crore in the September 22 quarter. There is a
rise in the
EPS of the company quarter on quarter year on year. If we look at the EPS here, then the
EPS of the company which has come out this time is around Rs.  The
EPS is 69, which is showing
growth in both quarter on quarter and year on year. So
guys,
if you look at the company's result, there is a downfall only in income.
Otherwise, the company has presented a very strong
result. Talking about segment wise revenue, there is
par life, par pension, non-par
life, non-par pension, non-par
variable, then non-par variable pension, war
label pension, then after that there is ANT non-
power, health. The
company generates revenue from many sectors. There are many
insurance policies through which the company
generates revenue.
This time, a very strong result has come. If we do
not count the income here, then if we cover its standalone
financial result, then the
income that has come out this time, guys,
if you look here, the income is
Rs 17526 crore, in the last quarter it was Rs
2354 crore and in the September 22 quarter, the
income is Rs 22904 crore. There has been a
downfall in quarter on quarter year on year. The
company has incurred expenses of Rs
17226 crore.  There was an expense of ₹2334 crore in the previous quarter
and ₹2381 crore in the September 22 quarter.
Income
is down, expenses have also come down quarter on
quarter year on year. After this, there is
operating profit, profit before tax
which is ₹248 crore, ₹208 crore in the previous quarter
and ₹1999 crore in the September 22 quarter. There has been an
increase in the quarter on quarter year on year. The
net profit of the company
presented this time is ₹244 crore, ₹
26.9 crore in the previous quarter and ₹
10099.4 crore in the September 22 quarter. There has been an
increase in the quarter on quarter year on year.
If we look at the EPS of the company this time, the
EPS that has come out this time is around ₹1.69. There is an
increase in both quarter on quarter and year on year. So guys, the
result of the company is overall a very
good result, there is just a decline in income
but there has been a very good growth in profit, so we
can say  Yes, this is an average result, so we will
end the video here. If you have any
doubt, ask in the comment box. We will meet
in the next video, till then bye bye.